<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kamoso.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كاموسو</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKamosoxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kamoso</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Kamoso</name>
  <summary>Use your webcam to take pictures and make videos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Useu la càmera web per prendre fotografies o fer vídeos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Useu la càmera web per prendre fotografies o fer vídeos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Používejte svou webkameru k pořizování snímků a videí</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Mit Kamoso können Sie mit Ihrer Webcam Bilder und Videos aufnehmen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Utilisez votre webcam pour prendre des photos et enregistrer des vidéos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Utilizza la tua webcam per scattare foto o registrare video</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Uw webcam te gebruiken om foto's of video's te maken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Use a sua Webcam para tirar fotografias ou criar vídeos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Använda din webbkamera för att ta bilder eller göra videor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Kamoso — чудова програма для використання вашої вебкамери для створення знімків або запису відео</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxUse your webcam to take pictures and make videosxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Kamoso is a simple and friendly program to use your camera. Use it to take pictures and make videos to share.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kamoso és un programa senzill i amigable per usar la càmera web. Useu-lo per prendre fotografies o fer vídeos per compartir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Kamoso és un programa senzill i amigable per usar la càmera web. Useu-lo per prendre fotografies o fer vídeos per compartir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kamoso est un programme simple et intuitif qui vous permettra d'utiliser votre caméra. Vous pouvez l'utiliser pour prendre des photos et enregistrer des vidéos afin de les partager.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kamoso è un programma semplice e amichevole per utilizzare la tua webcam. Utilizzalo per scattare foto o registrare video da condividere.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kamoso is een eenvoudig en vriendelijk programma om uw camera te gebruiken. Gebruik het om foto's en video's te maken en te delen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kamoso é um programa simples e amigável para usar a sua Webcam. Use-a para tirar fotografias ou criar vídeos para partilhar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kamoso är ett enkelt och trevligt program för att använda din kamera. Använd det för att ta bilder eller göra videor att dela med dig av.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kamoso — проста і дружня до користувача програма для використання вашої вебкамери для створення знімків або запису відео.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKamoso is a simple and friendly program to use your camera. Use it to take pictures and make videos to share.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Kamoso</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kamoso</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/stable/en/extragear-multimedia/kamoso/user-guide.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kamoso/kamoso.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kamoso</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
